[
  {
    "question": "1 x 2",
    "options": ["1", "2", "3"],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 2",
    "options": ["2", "4", "6"],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 2",
    "options": ["3", "6", "9"],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 2",
    "options": ["4", "8", "12"],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 2",
    "options": ["5", "10", "15"],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 2",
    "options": ["6", "12", "18"],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 2",
    "options": ["7", "14", "21"],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 2",
    "options": ["8", "16", "24"],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 2",
    "options": ["9", "18", "27"],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 2",
    "options": ["10", "20", "30"],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  }
]
